* Loans
    
    Loans
    -----
    
    Take control of your finances with a low-interest fixed-rate personal loan.

    ### Explore

    ### Calculators

    ### Articles

* Prosper® Card
    
    The Prosper® Card
    -----------------
    
    Built to help you take control of your credit

    ### Explore

    ### Articles

* Home Equity
    
    Home Equity
    -----------
    
    Turn your home equity into cash fast. Get your rate in minutes.

    ### Explore

    ### Calculators

    ### Articles

* Investing
    
    Investing
    ---------
    
    Diversify your portfolio—invest in personal loans.

    ### Explore

* More
    
    Explore Prosper
    ---------------
    
    Learn about products and services promoted or offered by our partners, more helpful resources, and all about Prosper.

    ### Insurance

    ### Tools & Resources

    ### Company

X

* Get started

Prosper Privacy Policy & Federal Privacy Notice
===============================================

Welcome to Prosper. We believe that consumers deserve the utmost respect when it comes to the privacy of their personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to Prosper Marketplace, Inc. and its wholly owned subsidiary, Prosper Funding LLC (together, “Prosper”, “we,” “us” or “our”).

We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, protect, and disclose information and data when you use Prosper’s websites, services, and mobile applications. This Privacy Policy also explains your choices for managing information preferences, including opting out of certain uses of your personal information. By accessing or using Prosper’s websites, mobile applications or services, you consent to this Privacy Policy.

If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, or if you need assistance in exercising any of your choices under this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

This policy applies to all current and former Prosper customers. Note that, in order to use our services, you must be 18 years of age or older. Our websites, services, and mobile applications are intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.

Effective January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) provides specific rights and protections to California residents. If you are a California resident, please see the section entitled “Notice to California Residents” below for more information.

INFORMATION PROSPER COLLECTS ABOUT YOU
--------------------------------------

**Information Provided by You**

We collect personal information about you that you provide while you use Prosper websites, including but not limited to, [www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/), [www.prospercards.com](https://www.prospercards.com/), [www.myprospercard.com](https://www.myprospercard.com/), or [www.prosperhealthcare.com](https://www.prosperhealthcare.com/) or any associated websites, desktop or mobile applications (collectively, the “Prosper website” or “Prosper websites”). We collect this information when you apply for credit or register as a borrower or investor. Additional information may be gathered during your subsequent use of the Prosper websites, or when we communicate with you via telephone, email or other means.

Certain personal information must be supplied when you apply for credit and/or register as a borrower or investor, or in connection with servicing your account, in order to meet our legal obligations, verify your identity, facilitate determinations for credit eligibility, protect against fraud, and complete your transaction. The following categories of information may be collected:

* Your basic identifying information (for example, your name, address, email, telephone number, and date of birth);
* Your Social Security number;
* Your employment and income information;
* Your bank account information;
* For a loan to be used with a merchant or service provider (e.g., a healthcare provider), the identity of the merchant or service provider and the name of the party that will receive the good or service;
* Other information you may provide in connection with a financial product or service, such as your demographic information (where permitted or required by applicable law) and the location and value of the property securing your loan;
* Government-issued identification or additional information for identity verification;
* Any personal information you provide us.

We may also collect information that you provide to us about your co-applicant in connection with a joint application or loan. By submitting information about someone other than yourself, you represent that you are authorized to provide us with that person’s information for the purposes identified in this Privacy Policy and/or in connection with our services.

In addition, we gather names, email addresses, and phone numbers of people who contact us with questions.  We collect this information only for the purpose of responding to inquiries.  If you use our “refer-a-friend” feature, we will collect information from you in order to process your referral request.

You may also provide your information to certain third-party financing platforms who will process your application for credit and may provide your information to us. The use of your information by that online financing platform is governed by that company’s privacy policy.

If you use the comments section of our blog on [www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/), you should be aware that information you submit is stored there and will be visible to other users of the Prosper websites.

Prosper collects consent to send text messages to customers. If you provide your consent for Prosper to send you text messages, Prosper will not pass this consent to other parties. Prosper does not purchase consent to send text messages to customers.

**Information Collected From Third Parties**

When you check your rate or apply for credit through Prosper, we will collect information from credit bureaus and other third parties to facilitate determinations for credit eligibility, perform analyses, provide you with marketing offers and assess risks related to extending credit to you and any co-applicant and, if you are a personal loan applicant, to help investors determine whether to commit to your personal loan. If you obtain a personal loan or credit card through Prosper, we also collect information throughout the life of your financial obligation through Prosper from credit bureaus and other third parties in order to assess risks associated with your financial obligation, perform analyses, provide information to investors interested in buying or selling your financial obligation, and to provide you with marketing offers. If another company refers you to Prosper or assists you in any way in the application process, we may also collect your information from that company in order to process your application.

The following categories of information are generally collected for personal loan, home equity, and credit card applicants, and customers:

* Your identifying and application information (for example, your name, address, email, telephone number, date of birth, social security number, and employment information);
* Your credit score, credit history and other information related to your creditworthiness, identity and financial transactions;
* Your bank account information and transactions;
* If you applied for a loan to be used with a merchant or service provider, information related to any dispute you submit regarding the merchant or service provider;
* If you applied for a loan or credit card that is processed through an online finance platform other than Prosper, the status and terms of your loan or loan offer through that platform;
* If you applied for a home equity product through Prosper, information related to your demographics (as required by law) and property, and any other information to evaluate and complete your application.

If you register as an investor through Prosper, we will collect information from credit bureaus and other third parties to verify your identity and bank account information and assess risks related to your account.  If another company refers you to Prosper or assists you in any way in the registration or investing process, we may also collect your information from that company in order to process your registration or request, or to update your account information.

**Information Gathered Based on Your Activity on the Prosper Websites**

In order to provide services to you, improve our business and maintain records required by law, Prosper collects information about your transactions and activity.  For personal loan borrowers, this includes your payment history.  For credit card customers, this includes your transaction data such as credit card purchases, payment or transaction history. For investors, this includes your fund transfers and purchases.  For all users, Prosper and/or its service providers collect information about your visits to [www.prosper.com](http://www.prosper.com/), [www.prospercards.com](https://prospercards.com/), [www.myprospercard.com](https://www.myprospercard.com/), or [www.prosperhealthcare.com](http://www.prosperhealthcare.com/) and other Prosper websites and the computer or device through which you access our websites, such as your IP address, geographical location, operating system, browser type, referral source, time and length of visit, button clicks and/or page views, and your mobile device identifier (IDFA or AAID). With respect to individuals that have not created user accounts with Prosper, we do not associate the information that we collect with an identifiable consumer or household.

For customers using our mobile apps, the mobile apps may periodically collect, transmit, and use geolocation information to enable certain features, including features that prevent fraudulent card use and send alerts, but only if you expressly authorize collection of such information. Geolocation information can be monitored on a continuous basis in the background only while the mobile app is being used or not at all, depending on your selection. You can change your location permissions at any time in your mobile device settings.

**_Tracking Technologies_**

Cookies and Web Beacons. Prosper and our marketing partners and service providers use technologies such as, but not limited to, cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, scripts and other similar technologies, that gather information on our website. That information is used for a variety of purposes, such as to analyze trends, administer the Prosper websites, track users’ movements around the Prosper websites, gather information about our user base as a whole, to understand how visitors interact with our websites, or to serve advertisements on our websites or on other websites. We may receive reports on this activity on an individual and aggregated basis.

We use cookies when you interact with Prosper websites to keep track of your personal session, help authenticate your account, and detect fraud. Cookies are also used to gather statistical data, such as which pages are frequently visited, what is downloaded, and the address of sites visited immediately before or after coming to Prosper websites. You can control the use of cookies by managing your cookie consent preferences when visiting our websites or within your web browser. However, if you reject cookies, your ability to use some features or areas of Prosper websites may be limited.

Usage Data & Site Activity.  Prosper also uses Local Storage, such as HTML5, to store content information and preferences. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5.

Third Party Technologies.  Prosper partners with third parties to manage our advertising services on other websites and evaluate overall Prosper website performance, and/or to collect certain information when you visit and interact with Prosper websites and services. These third party companies may use technologies, such as cookies, to recognize browsers and to gather information about your activities on Prosper websites and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests, or to help us track the success of our marketing efforts, your interactions with Prosper websites, and overall Prosper website performance. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out of certain advertising networks by clicking [here](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/).  Please note that this does not opt you out of receiving all ads and you may still encounter generic ads.

**_Do-Not-Track Signals_**

Prosper does not process or respond to “do not track” signals or other similar signals whereby a visitor to a website requests that it disable collection of information about the visitor’s online activities over time and across different websites.

HOW PROSPER USES YOUR INFORMATION
---------------------------------

**Processing Your Transaction/Providing You Services**

If you register as a borrower and/or request credit by applying for a personal loan, home equity product, or credit card, Prosper will use your information to facilitate your loan and/or request for credit, and other services provided to you.  This may include:

* Generating your account profile, processing your personal loan, home equity product, or credit card application and verifying your identity and application information;
* Assigning you a Prosper Rating or furnishing you with a credit score upon your request;
* Enabling automatic payments and fund transfers with other financial institutions;
* Implementing collection activities as needed;
* Communicating with you concerning your personal loan, home equity product, or credit card application, account, and/or transactions;
* Addressing any disputes you may raise.

If you register as an individual investor, Prosper will use your information to facilitate marketplace investing.  This may include:

* Generating your investor profile;
* Enabling automatic payments and fund transfers with other financial institutions;
* Communicating with you concerning your Prosper account and transactions;
* Addressing any disputes you may raise.

**Analysis & Data Optimization**

Prosper uses your information to conduct analyses related to our services and Prosper websites.  We use this information to improve credit models and our services.  We also use this information to improve Prosper websites’ usability and to evaluate the success of particular marketing campaigns and other activities.

**Marketing & Surveys**

Prosper may use your personal information to select you for certain marketing communications, newsletters, surveys and/or requests for feedback regarding your experience.  Prosper may use your personal information both to select you for offers and to communicate offers to you.

**_Optional Marketing Communications_**

**Receipt of** **marketing** **communications via email is voluntary.**   **If you do not wish to receive these communications****,** **you may unsubscribe using the link in any marketing email that Prosper sends to you. Personal loan and investor customers may also** **sign in at www.prosper.com, select “Settings” from the drop-down menu,** **and** **disable** **unwanted communication** **types in the section titled** **“Communication Preferences.” All consumers may contact us at** [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) **and we will assist you in disabling** **optional** **communications**. **Please note that for personal loan applicants and borrowers, your opt-out choices will not apply to your co-borrower.**

HOW PROSPER SHARES YOUR INFORMATION
-----------------------------------

We will share your personal information with nonaffiliates (companies not related by common ownership or control) and among affiliates (companies related by common ownership or control, including but not limited to the companies covered by this policy) only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy.  By law, you are permitted to limit some types of sharing, but not others.

Prosper shares your information with third parties as permitted by law, including in the following specific ways:

* Lending Partners. All types of credit offered through Prosper are fulfilled by a third-party bank or non-bank lending partner that may extend credit to you (“Lending Partner”).  If you apply for a personal loan, home equity product, or credit card through Prosper, you are also providing your information to the potential Lending Partner, and further information may be provided to that Lending Partner after your loan originates or your card is issued.  The use of your information by your Lending Partner is governed by that Lending Partner’s privacy policy.

* Co-Applicants / Co-Borrowers. We may share certain limited information with your co-applicant / co-borrower in order to process your application and/or loan or service your account, and as needed to provide our services. 

* Third Party Service Providers. Prosper relies on third party service providers to help us conduct our business and marketing activities, such as maintaining our files and records, offering customer service, expanding access to our products, risk analysis, sending marketing communications, facilitating fund transfers, collecting past due debt, or negotiating settlements for delinquent debt.  Prosper may share your information with such companies, which are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to Prosper.  Information may also be shared among affiliates (including but not limited to the companies covered by this policy) for this purpose where one affiliated company provides services to or on behalf of another affiliated company in connection with your account or application.

* Prosper Card account holders: We share your information with Fiserv Solutions, LLC (“Fiserv”) for processing, servicing, and other account services. If you create an online account at [prospercards.com](http://www.prospercards.com/) and/or [www.myprospercard.com](http://www.myprospercard.com/), Fiserv will directly collect information provided by you via these sites, and may use that information according to the terms of Fiserv’s privacy policy, including for Fiserv’s own business purposes. By agreeing to Prosper’s Privacy Policy, you also agree to be bound by Fiserv’s privacy policy and consent to the use of your information provided via the aforementioned sites for Fiserv’s own business purposes. Fiserv’s privacy policy may be found here: [https://www.fiserv.com/en/about-fiserv/privacy-notice.html](https://www.fiserv.com/en/about-fiserv/privacy-notice.html)

* Potential Purchasers of Personal Loans. Prosper shares your information, including your Prosper Borrower Rating, on an anonymous basis to allow potential purchasers to decide whether to commit to your personal loan.  This information is also contained anonymously in personal loan data files available through Prosper’s Developer Tools and Marketplace Performance pages.  Although your credit information is displayed, your identity is never shared with investors until your personal loan has been purchased. 

* Loan Purchasers. If your personal or credit card loan originated through our platform is sold, we may provide the purchaser of your loan and their agents with your personal and credit information and loan identifier(s). Personal information is released to (1) personal loan purchasers; (2) qualified financial institutions with adequate protections to safeguard your personal information (“Qualified Institutions”); (3) service providers of Qualified Institutions; (4) Qualified Institutions that participate in structured deals; (5) debt buyers; and (6) auditors of purchasers, their lenders, or regulators.  In some cases, these purchasers may also provide targeted marketing to you.  Information provided to investors in connection with sales of our fractional Borrower Payment Dependent Notes (“Notes”) will not include personal identifying information.  For more information on Notes, please see our [Prospectus](https://www.prosper.com/prospectus).

* Referral Partners. If you were referred to Prosper by another company (a “Referral Partner”) or person, Prosper will share your information as necessary to honor the terms of its agreement with that Referral Partner or person and to process your transaction.  In some cases, Prosper may share your information with a Referral Partner for that Referral Partner’s own business purposes, such as to analyze and improve its business and provide marketing. Your rights with respect to this sharing are discussed in the federal Gramm-Leach-Bliley Privacy Notice at the end of this policy.

* Merchants or Service Providers. If you applied for a loan to be used with a merchant or service provider, Prosper may share your information with the merchant or service provider associated with your loan application. 

* Credit Bureaus. Prosper may share your personal information with credit bureaus to meet our credit reporting obligations.

* Affiliates. Prosper affiliates, including entities covered by this policy and other companies related by common ownership or control may share your information with each other, including information related to your creditworthiness, for purposes of general business analysis or to present targeted marketing to you or others.  Your rights with respect to this sharing are discussed in the federal Gramm-Leach-Bliley Privacy Notice at the end of this policy.

* Your Consent. Prosper may share your personal information with third parties at your direction or whenever you consent.

* Legal Requests & Regulatory Requirements. Prosper may share your personal information to comply with, or to allow investors or potential investors to comply with, any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or regulatory or governmental request. Prosper may also share your personal information for the purposes of limiting fraud, or in connection with an audit or the sale of Prosper to a third party.
* Sharing of Anonymized Data.  Prosper may share aggregated and anonymized data sets with third parties, including, but not limited to, business partners, service providers, loan purchasers, potential loan purchasers, and among Prosper affiliates.  No personally identifiable information will be included in these data sets.

ADDITIONAL FACTS ABOUT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
------------------------------------------------

**How you can change your personal information**

If you have applied for a personal loan or registered as an investor, you can access the personal information you have provided to us by logging in at [www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/), and navigating to the “Settings” page of your account.  As a registered investor, you can update your password, email, phone number, or home address at any time.  As a registered personal loan applicant or borrower, you may update your password, email, phone number, bank account information or mailing address at any time, though certain changes prior to loan origination may require you to submit a new loan application.  To change your information, you may also contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  We will respond to your request within a reasonable time.

Credit card applicants: You can change your contact information by calling our customer service at 1-800-851-0630.

Prosper Card account holders: You can change your contact information by calling our customer service at 1-800-903-4697.

Home equity applicants: You can access the contact information you have provided to us by logging in at [www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/), and navigating to the “Settings” page of your account.  To change application or other information, you may contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

For all customers, we will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, conduct analyses or audits, or to enforce our agreements or as otherwise permitted and/or required by law.

**How Prosper Secures Your Information**

Prosper uses significant safeguards, including physical, technical (electronic), and operational controls to protect your personal information, both during transmission and once received.  If you have any questions about the security of your information, you can contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Prosper equips all servers with a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) certificate to ensure that when you connect to our websites, you can tell that you are on a Prosper website and that all data entered into the websites are transmitted to us in a secure encrypted channel. Once on our system, personal information can only be read or written through defined service access points, the use of which is password-protected.  Data security is achieved through technical safeguards that include a combination of encryption, firewalls, intrusion prevention system, malware detection system, and data loss prevention systems.  Prosper also conducts vulnerability scans of applications and systems regularly. 

Access to the system is tightly controlled and limited to only those who have a need to access information.  Administrative safeguards such as a security awareness program, background checks, and internal information use policy ensure that only trained and trusted staff are permitted to access personal information.  Some additional features of our security program include:

**S_ecure Data Center_**

We store all sensitive financial information in state-of-the-art, highly secure data centers that are audited per AICPA SOC for Service Organizations. Physical access to the data centers is strictly controlled and we use the latest threat prevention technologies such as network and web application firewalls, VPN, antivirus, Web filtering and antispam technologies.

**_Session Time-Outs_**

We employ session time-outs to protect your account or application. You will be logged out of the site automatically after a specified period of inactivity. This time-out feature reduces the risk of others being able to access your account or information if you leave your computer unattended.

**_Account Authentication_**

If you have an account, at a minimum, we require that you use a password or follow other secure steps we have instituted to allow you to access your account. If you create a password, you must use both numbers and letters in your password. We have also instituted secure steps by which you can regain access to your account should you forget your password. You should always choose a password that is difficult for others to guess and change your password frequently. 

**Additional Steps You Should Take to Ensure the Security of Your Information**

Prosper sends important communications regarding your account or application via email.  You should therefore take steps to secure and restrict access to your email account and change your email account password frequently.  You should also be aware of fraudulent emails known as “phishing,” from companies claiming to be Prosper and requesting your login information or other account information.  Prosper will never ask for your login information in an email.  

When you are finished using Prosper websites, you should log out completely, then close the browser window and clear the browser’s cache files and saved passwords.  This step is particularly important if you use a computer that is accessed by other people, such as in a public library or Internet café.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Any updates to the Privacy Policy become effective when posted on Prosper websites.  If we make any material changes, we will notify you by email or by providing the revised Privacy Policy in your account on [www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/) if you have one. Your continued use of our services following the update means that you accept Prosper’s updated Privacy Policy.

For additional information, or if you have any questions regarding this policy or the privacy practices at Prosper, please submit your questions or comments directly to [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Note: Prosper Marketplace, Inc. is the parent company of Prosper Funding LLC.  Prosper Funding LLC owns the Prosper platform and website ([www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/)) and application as well as loans underlying all borrower payment dependent notes.  Prosper Marketplace, Inc. operates the Prosper platform and provides administrative support to Prosper Funding LLC. 

You can also send questions or comments to:

Prosper Marketplace, Inc.  
Attn: Compliance Department  
221 Main Street, Suite 300  
San Francisco, CA 94105

1-855-755-1919

Effective date: June 10, 2024

NOTICE AT COLLECTION & PRIVACY NOTICE (CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS)
------------------------------------------------------------

Effective January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”) provides specific rights to California residents related to their “personal information,” as defined under the CCPA. Please note that the CCPA, and this Notice, do not apply to information covered by other federal and state privacy laws, such as the federal Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (“GLBA”), the California Financial Information Privacy Act (“CFIPA”), the Fair Credit Reporting Act, and certain other laws. This Notice applies solely to California residents and this Notice describes how Prosper collects, uses, and discloses information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you or your household (“personal information”).

**Categories and Sources of Personal Information**

_Categories of Personal Information that Prosper may collect about you_: Prosper may collect and process the following categories of personal information from you: when you apply for credit or register as a borrower or investor; when you respond to surveys or questionnaires; in connection with servicing your account; in order to meet our legal obligations; to verify your identity, facilitate determinations for credit eligibility, protect against fraud, and complete your transaction:

* **Identifiers**, including real name, telephone number, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifiers, e-mail address, internet protocol (“IP”) address, driver’s license, social security number, state identification card, passport number, signature, bank account numbers, and other similar identifiers.
* **Personal Information** Categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code §1798.80(e)), including certain information already listed in “Identifiers” above.
* **Characteristics of protected classification**, including date of birth/age, gender, military or veteran status, marital status, nationality, citizenship.
* **Sensitive Personal Information**, including social security number, driver’s license, state identification card, passport number, race, age, national origin, disability, gender, and veteran status.
* **Professional or Employment Information**, including current or past job history and salary.
* **Education information**, including details of your education.
* **Commercial information**, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
* **Audio and Visual Information**, including audio, electronic, or similar information we capture through your communications with us, e.g., voice recordings of telephone conversations, emails and instant messaging.
* **Inferences**, including any derivation of information, data, assumptions, or conclusions drawn from certain of the above categories used to create a profile reflecting the individual’s preferences, characteristics, behavior, or other similar trends.

This information is collected and processed by Prosper, our third-party service providers and certain third-party financing platforms who will process your application for credit and may provide your information to us. We collect and process this information in order to (i) process your application for credit, (ii) service your account, (iii) meet our legal obligations, (iv) verify your identity, (v) facilitate determinations for credit eligibility, (vi) protect against fraud, (vii) complete your transaction, (viii) conduct internal research and analysis, (ix) improve our websites and services, (x) to present you with promotions, advertisements and other marketing communications, and offers, and (xi) in some cases communicate responses back to you.

_Information about your interactions with our website and the mobile application_: For all users, Prosper collects information about your interactions with our homepage, landing pages, other Prosper websites that you may visit prior to beginning the registration and/or application process, and information about the device you use to access the website and the mobile application. This includes:

* **Identifiers**, such as IP address, mobile device identifier (IDFA or AAID), operating system, and browser type.
* **Internet or electronic network activity**, including your click movements on the webpage and the mobile application, referral source, time and length of visit, button clicks and/or page views, browsing history and information regarding your interaction with a website, application or advertisement.
* **Geolocation data**.

This information is collected by Prosper and our third party service providers, who work with us to track your interactions on these pages. We collect and process this information in order to (i) help ensure the security and integrity of our websites; (ii) identify and fix errors that affect the functionality of our websites; (iii) conduct internal research and analysis; (iv) determine eligibility for products and services; and (v) improve our websites and services.

_Information from third parties for marketing:_ For certain consumers, we may work with marketing service providers to obtain your personal information. We collect and process the following personal information:

* **Identifiers**, including your name, address, and email address.
* **Internet or electronic network activity**, including your browsing history and information regarding your interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.

We collect and process this information for marketing purposes in order to present you with offers, promotions, advertisements and other marketing communications.

_Information from Business-to-Business Interactions_

We collect identifiers, such as the names and contact information, for the individual points of contact from our business partners, and from companies with which we consider conducting business.

We collect and process this information in order to communicate with companies with which we are conducting business or are considering conducting business.

**How Prosper Discloses Personal Information**

Prosper may disclose your personal information with the following categories of service providers and third parties to help us conduct the business purposes listed above:

* Our other employees. Prosper may disclose your personal information with our other employees consistent with the purposes identified above.
* Our affiliates. We may disclose your personal information with our affiliates consistent with the purposes identified above.
* Service providers. We may disclose your personal information with our service providers to provide services on our behalf, such marketing service providers and service providers that facilitate surveys, questionnaires, or contests on Prosper’s behalf. These third parties have access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
* Affiliate and business transfer. If Prosper is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your personal information may be transferred.
* Legal compliance and harm prevention. Prosper may disclose your personal information as we believe necessary (i) to comply with applicable law, rules and regulations; (ii) to enforce our contractual rights; (iii) to investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with our company; (iv) to protect and defend the rights, privacy, safety and property of Prosper, you or others; and (v) to respond to requests from courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, and other public and government authorities.

These service providers and third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to Prosper.

**Prosper’s Retention Policy**

It is our policy to not retain personal information for longer than is reasonably necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was collected. The criteria we use to determine the specific retention period include: the type of information collected, our business purposes for retaining the information, and the various legal and regulatory requirements.

**Sharing or Selling Your Personal Information**

Prosper may sell or share, as these terms are defined by the CCPA, your personal information with third parties for marketing purposes. The categories of personal information that we may sell or share are:

* **Identifiers**, including IP addresses, cookie identifiers, email address and other pseudonymous identifiers.
* **Internet or other electronic network activity information**.

We do not sell or share the personal information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age.

You may have the right to opt-out of this sharing. For more information on your personal information sell/share rights see [Do Not Sell / Share My Personal Information](https://privacyportal.onetrust.com/webform/65d4fda4-8a68-43df-ab7b-053bd3e6c780/b121e2c0-bd0e-4d7c-b5ed-ba82f277121f).

**Your Rights Under the CCPA**

California residents have the following rights under the CCPA:

1. **Right to Know/Access.** Before or when we collect your Personal Information, you have the right to know:
    
    * The categories of Personal Information we collect, the business or commercial purpose for which we collect and use the Personal Information, and whether we sell or share that information; and
    * How long we intend to keep each category of Personal Information, including Sensitive Personal Information.
    
    In addition, you can ask us to give you information about our collection and use of your personal information. Specifically, you can request that we provide one or more of the following:
    
    * The categories of personal information we collected about you.
    * The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you.
    * Our business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing your personal information.
    * The categories of third parties to whom we disclose that personal information.
    * If we sold or shared your Personal Information, which we do not, the categories of Personal Information that we collected and shared about you and, for each category identified the categories of third parties to which we shared that particular category of Personal Information.
    * If we disclosed your personal information for a business purpose, the personal information categories that each category of recipients obtained.
    * The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.
2. **Right to Delete.** Subject to certain limitations, you can ask us to delete your personal information. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see “How You Can Exercise Your Rights Under CCPA”), we will delete your personal information from our records, and direct our service providers to do the same, unless an exception applies.
3. **Right to Correct.** You can ask us to correct inaccurate personal information that we have about you. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see “How You Can Exercise Your Rights Under CCPA”), we will use commercially reasonable efforts to correct inaccurate personal information and direct our service providers or contractors to do the same.
4. **Right to Opt-Out of Targeted Advertising**. You have the right to direct us to not “sell” or “share” your personal information (the “right to opt-out”).  We use technologies such as cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and other similar technologies, that gather information on our website. That information is used for a variety of purposes, such as to understand how visitors interact with our websites, or to serve advertisements on our websites or on other websites. The use of technologies, such as cookies, constitutes a ‘share’ or ‘sale’ of personal information under the CCPA. You can stop the use of certain third-party tracking technologies that are not considered our service providers by managing your cookie consent preferences when visiting our websites or by clicking on “Do Not Sell/Share My Information” at the bottom of www.prosper.com. Note that due to technological limitations, if you visit our website from a different computer or device, or clear cookies on your browser that store your preferences, you will need to return to this screen to opt-out and/or rebroadcast the signal.
5. **The Right to Limit the Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information.**  If we collect Sensitive Personal Information and use such information for reasons that are not aligned with the purposes for which we obtained it, then you have the right to limit the use and disclosure of such Sensitive Personal Information.  However, we can use this information as permitted by law, to follow the law, and to give you the best service.
6. **The right to Non-Discrimination or Non-Retaliation,** which means we cannot discriminate or retaliate against you if you exercise your rights under the CCPA.

We may, however, offer you certain financial incentives permitted by the CCPA that can result in different prices, rates, or quality levels. Such financial incentives may include gift cards, credits, and other monetary offerings; additional details related to the material terms of these financial incentives will be provided to you at the time the incentive is presented to you. Any CCPA-permitted financial incentive we offer will reasonably relate to your personal information’s value and contain written terms that describe the program’s material aspects. Participation in a financial incentive program requires your prior opt in consent, which you may revoke at any time.

**How You Can Exercise Your Rights Under CCPA**

To exercise one or more of your rights, you or your authorized agent may submit a verifiable consumer request in one of the following ways:

* If you are a personal loan customer, home equity applicant and/or investor, you may exercise these rights by signing into your Prosper account, selecting “Settings” from the drop-down menu and submitting your requests under “California Consumer Privacy Act”.
* If you are a Prosper Card account holder, you may contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a brief description of your request.
* If you do not have a Prosper account, you may contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a brief description of your request.
* If you are or were an employee or other representative for a company that did business with Prosper, please identify the company for which you are or were a representative.

Please note that if you contact us with your request via email we may request additional information from you or your authorized representative as needed to authenticate your request. You may only make a verifiable consumer request to know or request for access twice within a 12-month period.

The verifiable consumer request must do the following:

* Provide sufficient information to allow us to reasonably verify that you are the person about whom we collected personal information or that you are an authorized representative.
* Describe your request with sufficient detail so that we can properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

Upon receiving a request to know/request for access or a request for deletion, we will confirm receipt within 10 days.  If we can verify your request, we will make our best effort to respond within forty-five (45) days of our receipt of your request. If we require more time (up to 45 additional days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. Additionally, in our response, we will specify the manner in which we have deleted your personal information, in accordance with the CCPA.

We will not disclose information to you or delete information if we cannot verify your identity.

* * *

**How California Residents Can Designate an Authorized Representative**

Only you as a California resident, or a person that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable request to know/request for access, request for deletion, or request to opt-out.

To appoint an authorized representative to submit requests on your behalf, please provide us with written instructions stating the identity of the authorized representative and your authorization to have the representative act on your behalf.  Please send the written instructions appointing your authorized representative to [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We may also request additional information from you as needed to authenticate your request. If an authorized representative is acting on your behalf to make a request to know/request for access, request for deletion, or request to opt-out, your representative may also contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a brief description of the request. Please note that we may request additional information from your representative as needed to authenticate your request.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Notice, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or at (855) 755-1919.

_Last updated June 10, 2024_

NOTICE AT COLLECTION & PRIVACY NOTICE (OREGON RESIDENTS)
--------------------------------------------------------

Effective July 1, 2024, the Oregon Consumer Privacy Act (“OCPA”) provides specific rights to Oregon residents related to their “personal data,” as defined under the OCPA. Please note that the OCPA, and this Notice, do not apply to information covered by other federal and state privacy laws, such as the federal Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (“GLBA”), the Fair Credit Reporting Act, and certain other laws.  This Notice applies solely to Oregon residents and this Notice describes how Prosper collects, uses, and discloses data that identifies, is linked to or is reasonably linkable to you or your household (“personal data” or “personal information”).

The information on this page complements the notices and disclosures regarding your rights under federal laws and regulations (e.g., the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act). For more information, please visit https://www.prosper.com/legal/privacy-policy.

**Categories of Personal Data Collected by Prosper and Shared with Third Parties**

_Categories of Personal Information that Prosper may collect about you_: Prosper may collect and process the following categories of personal information from you: when you apply for credit or register as a borrower or investor; when you respond to surveys or questionnaires; in connection with servicing your account; in order to meet our legal obligations; to verify your identity, facilitate determinations for credit eligibility, protect against fraud, and complete your transaction:

* **Identifiers**, including real name, telephone number, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifiers, e-mail address, internet protocol (“IP”) address, driver’s license, social security number, state identification card, passport number, signature, bank account numbers, and other similar identifiers.
* **Characteristics of protected classification**, including date of birth/age, gender, military or veteran status, marital status, nationality, citizenship.
* **Sensitive Personal Information**, including social security number, driver’s license, state identification card, passport number, race, age, national origin, disability, gender, and veteran status.
* **Professional or Employment Information**, including current or past job history and salary.
* **Education information**, including details of your education.
* **Commercial information**, including records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
* **Audio and Visual Information**, including audio, electronic, or similar information we capture through your communications with us, e.g., voice recordings of telephone conversations, emails and instant messaging.
* **Inferences**, including any derivation of information, data, assumptions, or conclusions drawn from certain of the above categories used to create a profile reflecting the individual’s preferences, characteristics, behavior, or other similar trends.

This data is collected and processed by Prosper, our third-party service providers and certain third-party financing platforms who will process your application for credit and may provide your information to us. We collect and process this data for the following purposes: to (i) process your application for credit, (ii) service your account, (iii) meet our legal obligations, (iv) verify your identity, (v) facilitate determinations for credit eligibility, (vi) protect against fraud, (vii) complete your transaction, (viii) conduct internal research and analysis, (ix) improve our websites and services, (x) to present you with promotions, advertisements and other marketing communications, and offers and (xi) in some cases communicate responses back to you.

_Information about your interactions with our website and the mobile application_: For all users, Prosper collects information about your interactions with our homepage, landing pages, other Prosper websites that you may visit prior to beginning the registration and/or application process, and information about the device you use to access the website and the mobile application. This includes:

* **Identifiers**, such as IP address, mobile device identifier (IDFA or AAID), operating system, and browser type.
* **Internet or electronic network activity**, including your click movements on the webpage and the mobile application, referral source, time and length of visit, button clicks and/or page views, browsing history and information regarding your interaction with a website, application or advertisement.
* **Geolocation data**.

This information is collected by Prosper and our third party service providers, who work with us to track your interactions on these pages. We collect and process this information for the following purposes: to (i) help ensure the security and integrity of our websites; (ii) identify and fix errors that affect the functionality of our websites; (iii) conduct internal research and analysis; (iv) determine eligibility for products and services; and (v) improve our websites and services.

_Information from third parties for marketing_: For certain consumers, we may work with marketing service providers to obtain your personal information. We collect and process the following personal information:

* **Identifiers**, including your name, address, and email address.
* **Internet or electronic network activity**, including your browsing history and information regarding your interaction with a website, application, or advertisement.

We collect and process this information for marketing purposes in order to present you with offers, promotions, advertisements and other marketing communications.

_Information from Business-to-Business Interactions_: We collect identifiers, such as the names and contact information, for the individual points of contact from our business partners, and from companies with which we consider conducting business.

We collect and process this information for the purpose of communicating with companies with which we are conducting business or are considering conducting business.

**How Prosper Discloses Personal Data to Third Parties**

Prosper may disclose your personal data with the following categories of service providers and third parties to help us conduct the business purposes listed above:

* Our other employees. Prosper may disclose your personal information with our other employees consistent with the purposes identified above.
* Our affiliates. We may disclose your personal information with our affiliates consistent with the purposes identified above.
* Service providers. We may disclose your personal information with our service providers to provide services on our behalf, such as marketing service providers and service providers that facilitate surveys, questionnaires, or contests on Prosper’s behalf. These third parties have access to your personal information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
* Third party marketing partners. We may disclose your personal information with third parties for cross-context behavioral advertising.
* Affiliate and business transfer. If Prosper is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your personal information may be transferred.
* Legal compliance and harm prevention. Prosper may disclose your personal information as we believe necessary (i) to comply with applicable law, rules and regulations; (ii) to enforce our contractual rights; (iii) to investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with our company; (iv) to protect and defend the rights, privacy, safety and property of Prosper, you or others; and (v) to respond to requests from courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, and other public and government authorities.

These service providers and third parties are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to Prosper or as required by applicable law.

**Processing Your Personal Data for Targeted Advertising**

Prosper may sell or share, as these terms are defined by the OCPA, your personal data with third parties for marketing purposes. The categories of personal information that we may sell or share are:

* **Identifiers**, including IP addresses, cookie identifiers, email address and other pseudonymous identifiers.
* **Internet or other electronic network activity information**.

We do not sell or share the personal information of consumers we actually know are less than 16 years of age.

You may have the right to opt-out of this sharing. For more information on your personal information sell/share rights and the opt-out procedure visit Do Not Sell / Share My Personal Information.

**Your Rights Under the OCPA**

Oregon residents have the following rights under the OCPA:

1. **Right to Know/Access**. You have the right to ask us to confirm whether we are processing or have processed your personal data and the categories of personal data that we are processing or have processed. Specifically, you can request that we provide a copy of the categories and specific pieces of personal data that we have processed or are processing.
2. **Right to Delete**. Subject to certain limitations, you can ask us to delete your personal information. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see “How You Can Exercise Your Rights Under OCPA”), we will delete your personal information from our records, and direct our service providers to do the same, unless an exception applies.
3. **Right to Correct**. You can ask us to correct inaccurate personal information that we have about you. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request (see “How You Can Exercise Your Rights Under OCPA”), we will use commercially reasonable efforts to correct inaccurate personal information and direct our service providers or contractors to do the same.
4. **Right to Opt-Out of Processing of Personal Data for Purposes of Targeted Advertising, Selling, or Profiling**. You have the right to direct us to not process your personal data for the purposes of targeted advertising, selling your personal data, or profiling. We do not use your personal data to profile you in furtherance of decisions that produce legal effects or effects of similar significance.
    
    We use technologies such as cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and other similar technologies, that gather information on our website. That information is used for a variety of purposes, such as to understand how visitors interact with our websites, or to serve advertisements on our websites or on other websites. The use of technologies, such as cookies, constitutes “targeted advertising” under the OCPA. You can stop the use of certain third-party tracking technologies that are not considered our service providers by managing your cookie consent preferences when visiting our websites or by clicking on “Do Not Sell/Share My Information” at the bottom of www.prosper.com. Note that due to technological limitations, if you visit our website from a different computer or device, or clear cookies on your browser that store your preferences, you will need to return to this screen to opt-out and/or rebroadcast the signal.
    
5. **The right to Non-Discrimination**, which means we cannot discriminate against you if you exercise your rights under the OCPA by means such as denying goods or services, charging different prices or rates for goods or services or providing a different level of quality or selection of goods or services to the consumer.

**How You Can Exercise Your Rights Under OCPA**

To exercise one or more of your rights, you or your authorized agent may submit a verifiable consumer request in one of the following ways:

* If you are a personal loan customer, home equity applicant and/or investor, you may exercise these rights by signing into your Prosper account, selecting “Settings” from the drop-down menu and submitting your requests under “Oregon Consumer Privacy Act”.
* If you are a Prosper Card account holder, you may contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a brief description of your request.
* If you do not have a Prosper account, you may contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a brief description of your request.
* If you are or were an employee or other representative for a company that did business with Prosper, please identify the company for which you are or were a representative.

Please note that if you contact us with your request via email we may request additional information from you or your authorized representative as needed to authenticate your request.

The verifiable consumer request must do the following:

* Provide sufficient information to allow us to reasonably verify that you are the person about whom we collected personal information or that you are an authorized representative.
* Describe your request with sufficient detail so that we can properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.

Upon receiving a request to know/request for access or a request for deletion, we will confirm receipt within 10 days.  If we can verify your request, we will make our best effort to respond within forty-five (45) days of our receipt of your request. If we require more time (up to 45 additional days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing. Additionally, in our response, we will specify the manner in which we have deleted your personal information, in accordance with the OCPA.

We will not disclose information to you or delete information if we cannot verify your identity.

**Your Right to Appeal Our Decision**

You have the right to appeal our decision to refuse to take action on your request. You may exercise your right to appeal by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a brief description of your appeal request. You may exercise your right to appeal up to 30 days after receiving our response to your initial request. Upon receiving your appeal request, we will respond within forty-five (45) days of our receipt of your request.

**How Oregon Residents Can Designate an Authorized Representative**

Only you as an Oregon resident, or a person that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable request to know/request for access, request for deletion, or request to opt-out.

To appoint an authorized representative to submit requests on your behalf, please provide us with written instructions stating the identity of the authorized representative and your authorization to have the representative act on your behalf.  Please send the written instructions appointing your authorized representative to [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). We may also request additional information from you as needed to authenticate your request. If an authorized representative is acting on your behalf to make a request to know/request for access, request for deletion, or request to opt-out, your representative may also contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) with a brief description of the request. Please note that we may request additional information from your representative as needed to authenticate your request.

Your authorized agent may also exercise your right to opt-out of targeted advertising and stop the use of certain third-party tracking technologies that are not considered our service providers by managing your cookie consent preferences when visiting our websites or by clicking on “Do Not Sell/Share My Information” at the bottom of [www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/).

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Notice, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or at (855) 755-1919.

Last updated June 10, 2024

**Federal Privacy Notice** Rev. 05/2024

### FACTS

### WHAT DOES PROSPER DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

**Why?**

Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

**What?**

The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:

* Social Security Number and income
* Account balances and transaction history
* Credit history and credit scores

When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice

**How?**

All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons Prosper chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

### Reasons we can share your personal information

### Does Prosper share?

### Can you limit this sharing?

**For our everyday business purposes —**

such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus

Yes

No

**For our marketing purposes—**

to offer our products and services to you

Yes

No

**For joint marketing with other financial companies**

No

No

**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—**

information about your transactions and experiences

Yes

No

**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—**

Information about your creditworthiness

Yes

Yes

**For our affiliates to market to you**

Yes

Yes

**For nonaffiliates to market to you**

Yes

Yes

**To limit our sharing**

* Visit us online: [www.prosper.com](https://www.prosper.com/) – Personal loan and investor applicants/customers may limit our sharing of information by signing into your account, selecting “Settings” from the drop down menu, and disabling “Optional Information Sharing” in the section titled “Communication Preferences.”
* Email us: [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) and we will assist you in disabling such information sharing.

**Please note:**  
If you are a _new_ customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice (except where we have received your affirmative consent to begin sharing information sooner, through our privacy policy or otherwise). When you are _no longer_ our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.

**Questions?**

Email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or call us at 1-855-755-1919

### Who we are

**Who is providing this notice?**

Prosper Funding LLC

Prosper Marketplace, Inc.

### What we do

**How does Prosper protect my personal information?**

To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and building.

**How does Prosper collect my personal information?**

We collect your personal information, for example, when you

* Open an account or apply for financing
* Give us your income information and employment information
* Pay your bills

We also collect your information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.

**Why can’t I limit all sharing?**

Federal law gives you the right to limit only

* sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
* affiliates from using your information to market to you
* sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.  See below for more on your rights under state law.

**What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?**

Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.

### Definitions

**Affiliates**

Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies:

* _Our affiliates include companies with a Prosper name, such as Prosper Assets Holding LLC; and financial companies such as BillGuard, Inc_

**Nonaffiliates**

Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.

* _Nonaffiliates we share with can include financial services companies, marketing companies, and other service providers._

**Joint marketing**

A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you

* _Prosper doesn’t jointly market._

### Other Important Information

**Telephone Communications:** Prosper and its authorized agents, service providers, Lending Partners and partners may monitor and/or record all telephone communications in accordance with applicable law.

**Vermont Residents:** We will not disclose information about your creditworthiness to our affiliates and will not disclose your personal information, financial information, credit report, or health information to nonaffiliated third parties to market to you, other than as permitted by Vermont law, unless you authorize us to make those disclosures. Additional information concerning our privacy policies can be found at [https://www.prosper.com/legal/privacy-policy](https://www.prosper.com/legal/privacy-policy) or call 1-855-755-1919.

**Nevada Residents:** We are providing you this notice pursuant to state law. You may be placed on our internal Do Not Call List by calling 855-755-1919 or emailing [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Nevada law also requires us to provide you with the following to obtain additional information: Prosper Marketplace, Inc., 221 Main Street, Suite 300, San Francisco, CA 94105; Phone: 1-855-755-1919; E-mail: [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection); and Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington Street, Suite 3900, Las Vegas, NV 89101; Phone: 702.486.3132; Email: [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**North Dakota Residents**: We will not share information we collect about you with non-affiliated third parties, except as permitted by law, such as to process your transactions or to maintain your account.

**Texas Residents**: For questions or complaints about this loan, contact Prosper Marketplace Inc. at 855-755-1919 or [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). The lender is licensed and examined under Texas law by the Office of Consumer Credit Commissioner (OCCC), a state agency. If a complaint or question cannot be resolved by contacting the lender, consumers can contact the OCCC to file a complaint or ask a general credit-related question. OCCC address: 2601 N. Lamar Blvd., Austin, Texas 78705. Phone: (800) 538-1579. Fax: (512) 936-7610. Website: [occc.texas.gov](https://occc.texas.gov/). E-mail: [\[email protected\]](https://www.prosper.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Notes offered by Prospectus. Notes investors receive are dependent for payment on unsecured loans made to individual borrowers. Not FDIC-insured; investments may lose value; no Prosper or bank guarantee. Prosper does not verify all information provided by borrowers in listings. Investors should review the prospectus before investing.

**Invest**

Cookie Settings

Prosper Funding LLC

221 Main Street, Suite 300 | San Francisco, CA 94105

© 2005-2023 Prosper Funding LLC. All rights reserved.

### Received an offer code from us?

You’re in the right place! Get started by entering your offer code below.

Enter your 8-digit offer code  

Continue
